englishlinx.com 2018-11-09

# Englishlinx.com | Our Privacy Policies at Englishlinx.com

* * *

**Englishlinx.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

 **We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.**  
There may be occasions when Englishlinx.com obtains personally identifiable information to provide you with correspondence or otherwise. However, Englishlinx.com only gathers personally identifiable information, such as names, addresses, e-mail addresses, etc., when you voluntarily submit the same. You may choose to "opt-out" of receiving future mailings that we may make to you at any time.

Users should be aware that Englishlinx.com web sites might link them to the web sites of third parties. This privacy statement applies to the activities within Englishlinx.com web sites and does not apply to activities on the web sites of third parties.  
Englishlinx.com is not responsible for the activities or practices of those websites.

Englishlinx.com web servers automatically track IP addresses, platform types, domain names, and browser information for system administration. None of this data is personally identifiable. Englishlinx.com analyzes this data in the aggregate to determine how many visitors it has, and which web pages are of interest. Englishlinx.com uses this data to improve its web site, products, and services such that they remain appealing and viable.

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may place cookies our use your IP address or other aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number), about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**A Note to Parents**  
At Englishlinx.com, we are fully committed to complying with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. (Learn more about [COPPA compliance](http://www.coppa.org/).) Englishlinx.com strongly encourages all parents to supervise their children’s online activities and regularly monitor their children’s use of the Internet. Parents should monitor and supervise their children’s online use as well as their children’s online disclosure of their name, address or other personal information without parental consent.

**Copyright**  
© Englishlinx.com. All rights reserved. Any violation of copyright or intellectual property law is prohibited. The content provided by Englishlinx.com and the overall look and feel of the Englishlinx.com site and it's subsidiary sites are protected by U.S. copyright, trademark and other applicable intellectual property and proprietary rights laws and international treaties. Reproduction in whole or in part in any form or medium for use on another website or blog without express written permission of Englishlinx.com is prohibited. Teachers, students, homeschoolers, and parents my reproduce the worksheets for use in the classroom or personal use.

**Terms and Conditions**  
All visitors to this site are required to agree to these terms and conditions. If you do not agree, you should not use this site. By accessing the site you indicate your acknowledgment and acceptance of these terms and conditions. Englishlinx.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Check this page periodically for changes.

**No Warranties or Representations**  
These sites are provided by Englishlinx.com on an "as is" basis. Englishlinx.com makes no representations or warranties express or implied, to the information, services, products, and materials included on this site. Englishlinx.com disclaims all warranties, to the full extent permissible by applicable law, express or implied, including but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose. Englishlinx.com will not be liable for any damages arising from the use of this site, including but not limited to direct, indirect, incidental punitive and consequential damages.

|   
|   

Custom Search 

|   
---|---|---|---
